《S LINE》 (A red line connecting people who have had sex)
《خط S》 (خط أحمر يربط بين الأشخاص الذين مارسوا الجنس)
So sex...
لذا الجنس...
wrong
خطأ
There is a red line connecting people who have had sex.
هناك خط أحمر يربط بين الأشخاص الذين مارسوا الجنس.
So if you wear these glasses, you can see those red lines.
فإذا ارتديت هذه النظارات، يمكنك رؤية تلك الخطوط الحمراء.
You can see those red lines when you are born
يمكنك رؤية تلك الخطوط الحمراء عندما تولد
Hello
مرحبًا
This is too outrageous.
هذا أمر فظيع للغاية.
You high school students
أنتم طلاب المدرسة الثانوية
I know you are fearless
أنا أعلم أنك لا تخاف
I&amp;#39;m a criminal police officer.
أنا ضابط شرطة جنائية.
Don&amp;#39;t underestimate the detective
لا تقلل من شأن المحقق
I knew you wouldn&amp;#39;t believe it.
كنت أعلم أنك لن تصدق ذلك.
Wait a moment…
انتظر لحظة…
I never said I don&amp;#39;t believe you.
لم أقل أبدًا أنني لا أصدقك.
So you mean
فهل تقصد
After someone took Sun Ah&amp;#39;s glasses away
بعد أن أخذ أحدهم نظارات Sun Ah
Call her to the top floor and push her down?
اتصل بها إلى الطابق العلوي وادفعها إلى الأسفل؟
I think that&amp;#39;s it.
أعتقد أن هذا هو الأمر.
Who did it?
من فعل هذا؟
Why do this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
I don&amp;#39;t know either
انا لا اعرف ايضا
I can confirm that Sun Ah did not commit suicide
أستطيع أن أؤكد أن سون آه لم ينتحر
But she seems to have threatened many people with the fact that she could see the S line
لكن يبدو أنها هددت العديد من الناس بحقيقة أنها تستطيع رؤية خط S
Many people must have been threatened by her.
لا بد وأن العديد من الناس قد تعرضوا للتهديد بسببها.
So…
لذا…
Do you think it&amp;#39;s possible to have many pairs of glasses?
هل تعتقد أنه من الممكن أن يكون لديك العديد من النظارات؟
Because there have been several cases recently that are similar to the one committed by the guy who lives upstairs from you.
لأنه كانت هناك عدة حالات في الآونة الأخيرة مشابهة لتلك التي ارتكبها الرجل الذي يعيش في الطابق العلوي منك.
Why am I telling you this now?
لماذا أقول لك هذا الآن؟
Wait a moment
انتظر لحظة
Isn&amp;#39;t the world you see all red lines?
أليس العالم الذي تراه كله خطوط حمراء؟
Um
واحد
Almost all red lines
تقريبا كل الخطوط الحمراء
Oh... that&amp;#39;s why you wear sunglasses
أوه... لهذا السبب ترتدي النظارات الشمسية
You must be living a hard life...
لا بد أنك تعيش حياة صعبة...
Sun Ah
الشمس آه
Kang Sun-ah
كانغ سون آه
What are you doing
ماذا تفعل
No sleeping in class
لا نوم في الفصل
Focus on class
التركيز على الفصل
The human genome can be divided into body chromosomes and sex chromosomes
يمكن تقسيم الجينوم البشري إلى كروموسومات الجسم وكروموسومات الجنس
There is only one pair of sex chromosomes
هناك زوج واحد فقط من الكروموسومات الجنسية
The remaining 22 pairs are autosomes.
أما الأزواج الـ 22 المتبقية فهي عبارة عن صبغيات جسمية.
Autosomal chromosomes have nothing to do with sex inheritance
الكروموسومات الجسدية ليس لها علاقة بالوراثة الجنسية
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
What&amp;#39;s wrong
ما الخطب؟
Nothing
لا شئ
She just woke up screaming in the middle of her sleep in the classroom
لقد استيقظت للتو وهي تصرخ في منتصف نومها في الفصل الدراسي
Hello
مرحبًا
You&amp;#39;re just too weak.
أنت ضعيف جدًا.
Let&amp;#39;s go out and have some fresh air this weekend.
دعونا نخرج ونستمتع ببعض الهواء النقي في نهاية هذا الأسبوع.
no
لا
Why not?
ولم لا؟
If you don&amp;#39;t want to go, just say you don&amp;#39;t want to go.
إذا كنت لا تريد الذهاب، فقط قل أنك لا تريد الذهاب.
Because I have something to do
لأن لدي شيئا لأفعله
What&amp;#39;s up
ما الأمر
I&amp;#39;m going to work
انا ذاهب للعمل
What kind of job do you want to do?
ما نوع العمل الذي تريد القيام به؟
Don&amp;#39;t ask.
لا تسأل.
Maybe she doesn&amp;#39;t want to say it.
ربما أنها لا تريد أن تقول ذلك.
-Meishin Hotel - Meixing Hotel?
- فندق ميشين - فندق ميكسينج؟
Kim Mei-sung
كيم مي سونغ
I am here
أنا هنا
I asked you to make a new one for me.
طلبت منك أن تصنع لي واحدة جديدة.
You made a mistake again. What do you want?
لقد أخطأت مرة أخرى. ماذا تريد؟
You&amp;#39;re really driving me crazy
أنت حقا تقودني إلى الجنون
Go back and make a new one for me.
ارجع واصنع لي واحدة جديدة.
sorry
آسف
Those who have never even had sex are still there
أولئك الذين لم يمارسوا الجنس قط ما زالوا هناك
Meixing, where is your hometown?
ميكسينج، أين مسقط رأسك؟
Busan
بوسان
But you don&amp;#39;t have an accent at all.
ولكن ليس لديك لهجة على الإطلاق.
I put a lot of effort into correcting my accent.
لقد بذلت الكثير من الجهد في تصحيح لهجتي.
Is it necessary to do this?
هل من الضروري القيام بهذا؟
Because I want to be an actor and I&amp;#39;m preparing now
لأنني أريد أن أصبح ممثلًا وأنا أستعد الآن
You want an actor?
هل تريد ممثل؟
yes
نعم
I was also discovered by a scout on the road
لقد تم اكتشافي أيضًا بواسطة كشاف على الطريق
So that&amp;#39;s it
هذا هو الأمر إذن
Do you know if the music teacher has a girlfriend?
هل تعلم إذا كان للمعلم الموسيقى صديقة؟
Why are you interested in him?
لماذا أنت مهتم به؟
He looks so handsome
إنه يبدو وسيمًا جدًا
-Do you want me to ask him if he has a girlfriend? -Okay.
-هل تريد مني أن أسأله إذا كان لديه صديقة؟ -حسنا.
-Don&amp;#39;t ask? -Just eat your meal.
-لا تسأل؟ -فقط تناول وجبتك.
(Meishin Hotel)
(فندق ميشين)
Hi, I need to take a break.
مرحبًا، أحتاج إلى أخذ قسط من الراحة.
The total is 30,000 won
المجموع هو 30000 وون
Can&amp;#39;t we stay in a hotel?
ألا يمكننا البقاء في الفندق؟
Anyway, we&amp;#39;re only staying for a while and then we&amp;#39;ll leave. It doesn&amp;#39;t matter.
على أي حال، سنبقى هنا لفترة قصيرة فقط، ثم سنغادر. لا يهم.
Thanks
شكرًا
Last time I clearly said I was going to stay in a hotel
في المرة الأخيرة قلت بوضوح أنني سأبقى في فندق
Okay, I&amp;#39;ll take you there next time.
حسنًا، سآخذك إلى هناك في المرة القادمة.
(Kim Hye-young Bang Sung-jin) Kim Hye-young who bullies Sun-a
(كيم هي يونغ بانغ سونغ جين) كيم هي يونغ التي تتنمر على سون آه
(Jiang Shan&amp;#39;e) Pushed her down the stairs and ran away
(جيانغ شان إي) دفعها إلى أسفل الدرج وهرب
How could she disappear?
كيف يمكن أن تختفي؟
No card swipe or call records left
لم يتبق أي تمرير للبطاقة أو سجلات للمكالمات
Is it possible that
هل من الممكن أن
After the Chinese teacher pushed Shan&amp;#39;e down the stairs
بعد أن دفع المعلم الصيني شاني إلى أسفل الدرج
Suicide due to excessive self-blame
الانتحار بسبب اللوم الذاتي المفرط
This is the most convincing speculation so far.
وهذا هو التكهن الأكثر إقناعا حتى الآن.
Because the Chinese teacher&amp;#39;s last received message location was at school
لأن آخر رسالة استلمها المعلم الصيني كانت في المدرسة
but
لكن
Until the Chinese teacher&amp;#39;s body is found, he can only be considered missing.
حتى يتم العثور على جثة المعلم الصيني، لا يمكن اعتباره سوى مفقودًا.
And according to his family
وبحسب عائلته
He has a severe fear of heights.
لديه خوف شديد من المرتفعات.
So he would never push someone off a tall building.
لذلك لن يقوم أبدًا بدفع شخص من مبنى مرتفع.
Although we cannot accept this statement completely
على الرغم من أننا لا نستطيع قبول هذا البيان بشكل كامل
Who is the murderer?
من هو القاتل؟
Zhiyu
تشي يو
What if Sun-e...
ماذا لو كان صن-اي...
She won&amp;#39;t commit suicide.
إنها لن تنتحر.
I don&amp;#39;t mean to be opinionated.
لا أقصد أن أكون صاحب رأي.
But I always feel that something is weird
ولكنني أشعر دائمًا أن هناك شيئًا غريبًا
(Glasses?)
(نظارات؟)
Sun Ah becomes a different person after wearing glasses
تصبح سون آه شخصًا مختلفًا بعد ارتداء النظارات
What&amp;#39;s the magic of those glasses?
ما هو سحر تلك النظارات؟
Tell you secretly
أخبرك سرا
Just put on a pair of glasses
فقط ضع زوجًا من النظارات
You can find out who you had sex with.
يمكنك معرفة من مارست الجنس معه.
Really
حقًا
Do you think it will be true?
هل تعتقد أن هذا سيكون صحيحا؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Do you want accommodation?
هل تريد سكن؟
right
يمين
The total is 60,000 won
المجموع هو 60،000 وون
Clang
رنين
How come you guys are here?
كيف وصلتم إلى هنا؟
Hello
مرحبًا
Of course I have to visit my friends when they are working.
بالطبع يجب علي أن أزور أصدقائي عندما يعملون.
You are underage and cannot come here.
أنت قاصر ولا يمكنك المجيء إلى هنا.
Hello
مرحبًا
Aren&amp;#39;t you a minor?
ألست قاصراً؟
So...
لذا...
This is illegal
هذا غير قانوني
So,
لذا،
Are there any guests now?
هل هناك أي ضيوف الآن؟
Can I go up and take a look?
هل يمكنني الصعود وإلقاء نظرة؟
-Hello-Hello Hello
-مرحبا-مرحبا مرحبا
Keep your voice down.
أبقي صوتك منخفضا.
It&amp;#39;s so crowded
إنه مزدحم للغاية
It&amp;#39;s so crowded here
إنه مزدحم للغاية هنا
Hello
مرحبًا
So why do you have to run in?
فلماذا يجب عليك أن تركض؟
Very interesting
مثير للاهتمام للغاية
I always feel...very exciting
أنا دائما أشعر... بإثارة كبيرة
I need to rest
انا بحاجة للراحة
Please give me number 206
من فضلك أعطني الرقم 206
Is she coming alone?
هل هي قادمة لوحدها؟
(Room 206, Meixing Hotel)
(غرفة 206، فندق ميكسينج)
I think I&amp;#39;ve seen her somewhere.
أعتقد أنني رأيتها في مكان ما.
That&amp;#39;s right
هذا صحيح
I&amp;#39;ve had sex with many men.
لقد مارست الجنس مع العديد من الرجال.
but
لكن
Since you appeared
منذ ظهورك
Just having sex with strangers
مجرد ممارسة الجنس مع الغرباء
It can no longer fill my empty heart.
لم يعد بإمكانه ملء قلبي الفارغ.
I am scared
انا خائف
Afraid that I will always
خائفة من أنني سأظل دائما
Can&amp;#39;t get you
لا أستطيع الحصول عليك
I really want to make love
أريد حقا أن أمارس الحب
Neuropathy
اعتلال الأعصاب
I don&amp;#39;t even have a boyfriend.
ليس لدي حتى صديق.
Although not now, but there were many in the past
رغم أنه ليس الآن، ولكن كان هناك الكثير في الماضي
That&amp;#39;s not a boyfriend, that&amp;#39;s stalking
هذا ليس صديقًا، هذا مطاردة
You&amp;#39;ve never been in a relationship, yet you still talk so much
لم تكن في علاقة أبدًا، ومع ذلك لا تزال تتحدث كثيرًا
What&amp;#39;s wrong
ما الخطب؟
Yeah, that&amp;#39;s right.
نعم، هذا صحيح.
What
ماذا
The woman who just came here
المرأة التي جاءت للتو إلى هنا
We are a staff of the school administration office.
نحن أحد موظفي مكتب إدارة المدرسة.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
The one wearing glasses
الشخص الذي يرتدي النظارات
Are you sure it&amp;#39;s her?
هل أنت متأكد أنها هي؟
They are totally different.
إنهم مختلفون تماما.
But it can&amp;#39;t escape my sharp eyes
لكنها لا تستطيع الهروب من عيني الحادة
Can you keep your voice down?
هل تستطيع إبقاء صوتك منخفضا؟
(Hwagyeong-dong couple murder case)
(قضية قتل زوجين في هواجيونج دونج)
Shen Xianxi when she was a child
شين شيانشي عندما كانت طفلة
Mom killed Dad and ran away
أمي قتلت أبي وهربت
(The victim died on the spot) (Incident where the victim was killed with a kitchen knife)
(توفي الضحية على الفور) (حادثة قتل فيها الضحية بسكين المطبخ)
(It is speculated that the suspect learned about the victim&amp;#39;s affair) (Knowing that her father had an affair with the suspect&amp;#39;s sister, Yoo Jung-hye) (5-year-old daughter Shin Hyun-hye witnessed the scene)
(يُعتقد أن المشتبه به علم بعلاقة الضحية) (علمًا أن والدها كان على علاقة غرامية مع شقيقة المشتبه به، يو جونغ هيه) (كانت ابنته شين هيون هيه البالغة من العمر 5 سنوات شاهدة على المشهد)
(After witnessing the incident, he used imaginary lines to depict the scene of the affair)
(بعد أن شهد الحادثة، استخدم خطوطًا خيالية لتصوير مشهد الأمر)
I&amp;#39;m not being fooled by a psychopath.
أنا لا أخدع من قبل شخص مريض نفسيا.
I have a few questions
لدي بعض الأسئلة
Shan&amp;#39;e she...
شاني هي...
Is there an S line too?
هل هناك خط S أيضًا؟
That&amp;#39;s personal privacy.
هذه هي الخصوصية الشخصية.
So there is
لذلك هناك
That Shan&amp;#39;e&amp;#39;s S-line...
هذا هو خط S الخاص بشان...
With the classmate named Zhiyuan in your class
مع زميلك في الفصل المسمى تشي يوان
Is it connected?
هل هو متصل؟
no
لا
I don&amp;#39;t know who it&amp;#39;s connected to.
لا أعلم من هو المتصل به.
But
لكن
Not in our class
ليس في صفنا
I&amp;#39;m going crazy. Damn it.
أنا أجن. اللعنة.
Who do you think is connected to Sun Ah?
من تعتقد أنه مرتبط بـ Sun Ah؟
Is he the one who pushed Sun Ah down?
هل هو الذي دفع سون آه إلى الأسفل؟
right
يمين
It&amp;#39;s possible.
إنه ممكن.
(Random murder occurred in Gangam-dong area) Random murder occurred again in Gangam-dong area last night
(حدثت جريمة قتل عشوائية في منطقة جانجام دونج) وقعت جريمة قتل عشوائية مرة أخرى في منطقة جانجام دونج الليلة الماضية
Although the suspect was arrested immediately not far from the scene
على الرغم من أن المشتبه به تم القبض عليه على الفور ليس بعيدًا عن مكان الحادث
(The victim was arrested near the scene and died) Unfortunately, the victim died on the spot
(تم القبض على الضحية بالقرب من مكان الحادث وتوفي) وللأسف توفي الضحية على الفور
From the time the suspect was arrested at the scene
منذ لحظة القبض على المشتبه به في مكان الحادث
Even if a crime is committed
حتى لو ارتكبت جريمة
(It is expected that the drug poisoning cult will conduct multiple investigations) Still saying &amp;quot;I am now clean&amp;quot;
(ومن المتوقع أن تقوم طائفة التسمم بالمخدرات بإجراء تحقيقات متعددة) ولا تزال تقول "أنا نظيف الآن"
From the continuous laughter
من الضحك المستمر
Mental disorder cannot be ruled out...
لا يمكن استبعاد الاضطراب العقلي...
Is it possible to have more than one pair of glasses?
هل من الممكن أن يكون لدينا أكثر من زوج من النظارات؟
Glasses…
نظارات…
Are there several pairs?
هل هناك عدة أزواج؟
(Music Classroom)
(فصل الموسيقى)
Excuse me
اعذرني
The music is so beautiful
الموسيقى جميلة جداً
I can’t help but…
لا أستطيع المساعدة ولكن...
I envy you.
أنا أحسدك.
I know so much good music.
أعرف الكثير من الموسيقى الجيدة.
What&amp;#39;s the use of that?
ما الفائدة من ذلك؟
I still interact with students every day in school.
لا أزال أتفاعل مع الطلاب كل يوم في المدرسة.
Are you a beautiful star?
هل أنت نجمة جميلة؟
- You remember me? - Yes.
- هل تتذكرني؟ - نعم.
What is your dream?
ما هو حلمك؟
Guess what
خمين ما
I don&amp;#39;t think you want to stay in school forever.
لا أعتقد أنك تريد البقاء في المدرسة إلى الأبد.
Do you want to be an actor?
هل تريد أن تكون ممثلاً؟
Did I guess right?
هل خمنت بشكل صحيح؟
How do you know
كيف علمت بذلك
I think you are good at expressing things with your body.
أعتقد أنك جيد في التعبير عن الأشياء بجسدك.
You are right
أنت محق
It&amp;#39;s really magical
إنه أمر سحري حقًا
I really have confidence that I can do well.
لدي ثقة حقيقية بأنني أستطيع أن أفعل جيدا.
Those are natural.
هذه طبيعية.
Right?
يمين؟
Are you going home?
هل انت ذاهب الى المنزل؟
Um
واحد
Where is Kyungjin?
أين كيونغجين؟
She said she had something to do at home and left first
قالت إنها لديها شيء لتفعله في المنزل وغادرت أولاً
that…
الذي - التي…
are you free
هل أنت متفرّغة ؟
I see you like places where there are no people
أرى أنك تحب الأماكن التي لا يوجد بها أشخاص
How did you know this place?
كيف عرفت هذا المكان؟
I was on the swim team all the way through middle school.
لقد كنت في فريق السباحة طوال فترة المدرسة المتوسطة.
Although I don&amp;#39;t practice swimming
على الرغم من أنني لا أمارس السباحة
But sometimes I still sneak out to swim
ولكن في بعض الأحيان لا أزال أتسلل للسباحة
Can you swim
هل يمكنك السباحة
Won&amp;#39;t
لن
Hey, are you okay?
مهلا، هل أنت بخير؟
What is this?
ما هذا؟
(Spicy Cup Noodles)
(نودلز الكأس الحارة)
It&amp;#39;s all cooked. Eat it quickly.
لقد نضج كل شيء. تناوله بسرعة.
Delicious
لذيذ
But can we eat here?
ولكن هل يمكننا أن نأكل هنا؟
Well, as long as you don&amp;#39;t get caught.
حسنًا، طالما لم يتم القبض عليك.
If Lee Kyung-jin were here
لو كان لي كيونغ جين هنا
She will definitely say that she wants to use a gas stove to cook instant noodles.
ستقول بالتأكيد أنها تريد استخدام موقد الغاز لطهي المعكرونة الفورية.
But just now...
ولكن الآن...
Why would you jump in?
لماذا تريد أن تقفز؟
If you don&amp;#39;t want to talk, you don&amp;#39;t have to.
إذا كنت لا تريد التحدث، فلا داعي لذلك.
Feel sorry
أشعر بالأسف
I…
أنا…
From birth
منذ الولادة
You can see strange things
يمكنك رؤية أشياء غريبة
There are red lines on everyone&amp;#39;s head
هناك خطوط حمراء على رأس الجميع
Does it look like this?
هل يبدو مثل هذا؟
Um
واحد
So do I have one too?
فهل لدي واحدة أيضاً؟
You don&amp;#39;t
أنت لا تفعل
I don&amp;#39;t either
انا ايضا لا
Neither does Kyung-jin
ولا كيونغ جين أيضًا
Do you believe what I say?
هل تصدق ما أقول؟
Um
واحد
Why
لماذا
Because there&amp;#39;s no reason to lie.
لأنه ليس هناك سبب للكذب.
I&amp;#39;m weird, right?
أنا غريب، أليس كذلك؟
Um
واحد
Very unusual.
غير عادي للغاية.
It&amp;#39;s just as I thought.
إنه كما اعتقدت تمامًا.
Very handsome
وسيم جدا
I&amp;#39;m too ordinary.
أنا عادي جدًا.
Even if I disappear tomorrow, I don&amp;#39;t think anyone will notice
حتى لو اختفيت غدًا، لا أعتقد أن أحدًا سيلاحظ
If you disappear
إذا اختفيت
At least Jingzhen and I will know.
على الأقل أنا وجينغتشن سنعرف.
That is true.
هذا صحيح.
How many times do you want me to say
كم مرة تريدني أن أقول
- Just say it&amp;#39;s not me. - Yes
- فقط قل أنه ليس أنا. - نعم
Do I look like a fraud?
هل أبدو وكأنني محتال؟
Ms. Kang So-min
السيدة كانغ سو مين
Oh my god
يا إلهي
Zhiyu, long time no see.
تشيو، لم نلتقي منذ وقت طويل.
Long time no see
وقت طويل لا رؤية
Why don&amp;#39;t you answer my call? I miss you so much
لماذا لا ترد على مكالمتي؟ أفتقدك كثيرًا.
Well...
حسنًا...
No matter how much of a criminal I am, I still can&amp;#39;t...
بغض النظر عن مدى كوني مجرمًا، لا أستطيع أن أفعل أي شيء.
Wasn&amp;#39;t it the first time?
ألم تكن المرة الأولى؟
He was just a suspect then.
لقد كان مجرد مشتبه به حينها.
Are you the kind of person who picks on people?
هل أنت من النوع الذي يختار الناس؟
It&amp;#39;s over, right?
لقد انتهى الأمر، أليس كذلك؟
Can I go now?
هل يمكنني الذهاب الآن؟
good
جيد
Remember to answer my call
تذكر أن تجيب على مكالمتي
Bro, when exactly did you...
أخي متى بالضبط فعلت ذلك...
You don&amp;#39;t have to know
لا يجب عليك أن تعرف
(Lee Ji Won)
(لي جي وون)
(Kang Sun-ah&amp;#39;s boyfriend?)
(صديق كانج سون آه؟)
elder brother
الأخ الأكبر
But you don&amp;#39;t date girls?
ولكنك لا تواعد الفتيات؟
Am I dating anyone?
هل أنا أواعد أحدا؟
No, although we are not dating
لا، على الرغم من أننا لا نتواعد
But aren&amp;#39;t you always busy?
ولكن ألا تكون مشغولاً دائماً؟
That&amp;#39;s right.
هذا صحيح.
Is it the window period now?
هل هي فترة النافذة الآن؟
I&amp;#39;m curious about someone
أنا فضولي بشأن شخص ما
But I don&amp;#39;t want to sleep with her
ولكنني لا أريد أن أنام معها
Why dumbfounded
لماذا مذهول
What Why
ماذا لماذا
Can&amp;#39;t I have someone I&amp;#39;m simply curious about?
هل من الممكن أن يكون لدي شخص أشعر بالفضول تجاهه فقط؟
I need to rest
انا بحاجة للراحة
Please give me room 206
من فضلك أعطني الغرفة 206
That&amp;#39;s right
هذا صحيح
I have had sex with many men.
لقد مارست الجنس مع العديد من الرجال.
I&amp;#39;ve been with a lot of men
لقد كنت مع الكثير من الرجال
There are relationships
هناك علاقات
In the Beginning
في البداية
Even if there is only one room where I can lie down
حتى لو كانت هناك غرفة واحدة فقط حيث يمكنني الاستلقاء
I am very satisfied
أنا راضٍ جدًا
I even think that maybe tomorrow I will become a famous actor
حتى أنني أعتقد أنني ربما سأصبح ممثلًا مشهورًا غدًا
But then…
ولكن بعد ذلك…
My ears started to hurt.
بدأت أذناي تؤلمني.
I don&amp;#39;t mind the noises from other people next door.
لا أمانع في ضوضاء الأشخاص الآخرين المجاورين.
The problem is my voice
المشكلة في صوتي
Afraid of my actions
خائف من أفعالي
Make a sound with me
اصنع صوتًا معي
Will be heard by others
سوف يسمعها الآخرون
The same is true at school
والشيء نفسه ينطبق على المدرسة
I&amp;#39;m afraid someone will hear
أخشى أن يسمع أحد
The laughter I made when I looked at the teacher
الضحكة التي أطلقتها عندما نظرت إلى المعلم
Then I found this place
ثم وجدت هذا المكان
An old hotel that looks deserted in broad daylight
فندق قديم يبدو مهجورًا في وضح النهار
In this room I am free
في هذه الغرفة أنا حر
Then one day I found a pair of glasses
ثم في يوم من الأيام وجدت زوجًا من النظارات
I am perfect when I see through the glasses
أنا مثالي عندما أرى من خلال النظارات
Then at a certain moment
ثم في لحظة معينة
I became a spectator
لقد أصبحت متفرجًا
This room is perfect
هذه الغرفة مثالية
It&amp;#39;s my perfect world
إنه عالمي المثالي
Come on
تعال
But why did you suddenly come to the motel?
ولكن لماذا أتيت فجأة إلى الفندق؟
I just remembered the past.
لقد تذكرت الماضي فقط.
It&amp;#39;s quite fresh
إنه طازج تماما
Don&amp;#39;t you miss me?
هل تفتقدني؟
I&amp;#39;ll see you when I turn on the TV. There&amp;#39;s no need.
سأراك عندما أفتح التلفاز. لا داعي لذلك.
Really
حقًا
Are you leaving?
هل انت مغادر؟
How about the same time tomorrow?
ماذا عن نفس الوقت غدا؟
(Yin Junshan: Are you still at the Meixing Hotel today?) (Yes, I am at work.)
(يين جونشان: هل مازلت في فندق ميكسينج اليوم؟) (نعم، أنا في العمل.)
(Yin Junshan: Can I come over?)
(يين جونشان: هل يمكنني المجيء؟)
I want to extend my stay
أريد تمديد إقامتي
Room number
رقم الغرفة
Room 206
الغرفة 206
How is it suitable for me?
كيف هو مناسب لي؟
- You&amp;#39;re here. - Yes.
- أنت هنا. - نعم.
Teacher, you came early.
معلم لقد أتيت مبكرا.
Meixing?
ميكسينج؟
teacher
مدرس
This song
هذه الاغنية
It&amp;#39;s the song we listened to together back then.
إنها الأغنية التي استمعنا إليها معًا في ذلك الوقت.
How did you get here?
كيف وصلت إلى هنا؟
Teacher, I
معلم، أنا
I have something to confess to you.
عندي شيء أريد أن أعترف لك به.
What
ماذا
Teacher, I
معلم، أنا
I have been with many men
لقد كنت مع العديد من الرجال
Had a relationship
كان لدي علاقة
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
That&amp;#39;s right
هذا صحيح
I&amp;#39;ve had sex with a lot of men.
لقد مارست الجنس مع الكثير من الرجال.
but
لكن
Since you appeared
منذ ظهورك
Just having sex with a strange man
مجرد ممارسة الجنس مع رجل غريب
Can&amp;#39;t fill the emptiness in my heart
لا أستطيع ملء الفراغ في قلبي
I am scared
انا خائف
I’m afraid I’ll never...
أخشى أنني لن...
Can&amp;#39;t have you
لا يمكن أن يكون لديك
Are you crazy?
هل انت مجنون؟
A crazy woman indeed.
امرأة مجنونة بالفعل.
That&amp;#39;s right
هذا صحيح
I&amp;#39;ve had sex with a lot of men.
لقد مارست الجنس مع الكثير من الرجال.
Are you throwing it at me now?
هل ترميها علي الآن؟
right
يمين
Oh wait…
أوه انتظر…
What&amp;#39;s wrong with me?
ماذا بي؟
It feels so strange
إنه شعور غريب جدًا
I put drugs in the water in advance
أضع المخدرات في الماء مسبقًا
You&amp;#39;ll be fine soon.
سوف تكون بخير قريبا.
That&amp;#39;s right
هذا صحيح
I&amp;#39;ve been with a lot of men
لقد كنت مع الكثير من الرجال
Had a relationship
كان لدي علاقة
But since you showed up
ولكن منذ ظهورك
Just having sex with a strange man
مجرد ممارسة الجنس مع رجل غريب
Can&amp;#39;t fill the emptiness in my heart
لا أستطيع ملء الفراغ في قلبي
No, teacher
لا يا معلم
teacher
مدرس
Please
لو سمحت
That’s right…
هذا صحيح…
I have had sex with many men...
لقد مارست الجنس مع العديد من الرجال...
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Depend on
تعتمد على
A crazy woman hit me.
ضربتني امرأة مجنونة.
And took my clothes away
وأخذ ملابسي بعيدا
Fuck this crazy woman
اللعنة على هذه المرأة المجنونة
Where did you run to?
إلى أين ركضت؟
it hurts
إنه يؤلمني
Please help me call the police
من فضلك ساعدني في الاتصال بالشرطة
There&amp;#39;s nothing like glasses at the scene.
لا يوجد شيء مثل النظارات في هذا المشهد.
No
لا
Have you seen those people&amp;#39;s S lines?
هل رأيت خطوط S لهؤلاء الأشخاص؟
The employee sister originally only had one line
كانت أخت الموظفة في الأصل لديها خط واحد فقط
I don&amp;#39;t feel connected to my music teacher.
لا أشعر بالارتباط مع معلم الموسيقى الخاص بي.
Why do you do this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
have no idea…
ليس لدي أي فكرة…
Probably you will never know.
ربما لن تعرف أبدًا.
Do you think this incident is also related to glasses?
هل تعتقد أن هذه الحادثة مرتبطة بالنظارات أيضًا؟
No matter how you think about it, she always wears glasses in school
بغض النظر عن كيفية تفكيرك في الأمر، فهي ترتدي النظارات دائمًا في المدرسة
Looks like the glasses we&amp;#39;re looking for.
يبدو أن هذه هي النظارات التي نبحث عنها.
When she came to Meixing Hotel
عندما أتت إلى فندق ميكسينج
It looks completely different from when I was in school.
يبدو مختلفًا تمامًا عما كان عليه عندما كنت في المدرسة.
After she put on the glasses
بعد أن وضعت النظارات
You should feel special.
ينبغي أن تشعر بأنك مميز.
Mr. Detective
السيد المحقق
No one is exempt
لا أحد معفى
That&amp;#39;s why I say those glasses are dangerous.
ولهذا السبب أقول أن هذه النظارات خطيرة.
Mr. Detective
السيد المحقق
No one is exempt
لا أحد معفى
That&amp;#39;s why I say those glasses are dangerous.
ولهذا السبب أقول أن هذه النظارات خطيرة.
(Lee Soo Hyuk)
(لي سو هيوك)
(Center)
(مركز)
(And Lee Da Hee)
(ولي دا هي)
I was going to say this first.
كنت سأقول هذا أولاً.
Please give me
من فضلك أعطني
The moment I put on these glasses
لحظة ارتدائي لهذه النظارات
Wow...it turns out what you said is true
واو... اتضح أن ما قلته صحيح
So I got goosebumps all over my body
لذلك شعرت بقشعريرة في جميع أنحاء جسدي
I don&amp;#39;t believe you
انا لا اصدقك
Throw away those glasses immediately.
تخلص من تلك النظارات فورًا.
It seems that a sexual assault of a minor has occurred.
يبدو أن اعتداءً جنسياً على قاصر قد حدث.
Do you have sexual experience?
هل لديك تجربة جنسية؟
No
لا
Why did she lie?
لماذا كذبت؟
There seems to be a lot of things happening in school recently.
يبدو أن هناك الكثير من الأشياء تحدث في المدرسة مؤخرًا.
Mr. Detective
السيد المحقق
Is she single from birth?
هل هي عازبة منذ الولادة؟
You wear glasses.
أنت ترتدي النظارات.
Excuse me...are you free to have dinner with me soon?
عذرا... هل أنت متاح لتناول العشاء معي قريبا؟
What
ماذا
《S LINE》 (A red line connecting people who have had sex)
《خط S》 (خط أحمر يربط بين الأشخاص الذين مارسوا الجنس)